A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Staff Subject Files, Jon Funabiki FA1447
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC) Administrative Office Files, Meetings, and Reports, 1990-2007; 2
  - Computer Technology Factoid Project, undated (Box 57, Folder 479)
  - Grantmaking Chart, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 480)
  - Susan V. Berresford Teamwork Presentation, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 481)
  - Teamwork Expo (To EMAC Staff and Others), 1997 (Box 57, Folder 482)
  - EMAC Teamwork Project Presentation - Initative and Grant Support Teams, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 483)
  - Media and Diversity Meeting, 1996 October 22 (Box 57, Folder 484)
  - Correspondence - Media and Diversity, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 485)
  - Meeting on Civil Rights/Immigration/Race and the Media, 1997 December 11 (Box 57, Folder 486)
  - Council on Foundations Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 487)
  - Trustees on Journalism Ethics Initiative Presentation, 1998 January 28 (Box 57, Folder 488)
  - President's Commission on Race, 1997 December 17 (Box 57, Folder 489)
  - First Quarter Meeting, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 490)
  - American Society of Newspaper Editors (ASNE) Diversity Dialogue, 1998 January 30-31 (Box 57, Folder 491)
  - Women and Philanthropy Meetings at Ford Foundation, 1997 August 4 (Box 57, Folder 492)
  - Program Tools - Administrative Suggestions, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 493)
  - Journalists - Meeting on News Media Coverage of Civil Rights, Race, and Immigration Issues, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 494)
  - Vincent McGee, Susan Berresford Interview Sponsored by New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG), 1997 January 14 (Box 58, Folder 495)